噢  嘿  你们大家
Oh,hey,you guys?
我生日当天晚上订不到餐厅
I couldn't get a reservation for the night of my birthday..
所以我们要改到星期四晚上
so we'll have to do dinner Thursday night instead.
星期四  但那是万圣节耶
Thursday? But that's Halloween.
那又怎样
So?
只不过是很诡异而已
It's just spooky,that's all.
那  麦克也会跟我们吃晚餐吗
So,is Mike coming to dinner?
不会  我第一次可以跟男朋友过生日
No. It's my first birthday with a boyfriend,
他却要上班
and he has to work.
我很想对他发脾气
I'd get mad at him,
但是我想这会太快露出我的本性
but I think it's too soon to show my true colors.
菲比  你只预定5个人的餐位就可以了
Oh phobs, I would make the reservation for five.
我们其中一个要留下来照顾艾玛
Because one of us has to stay with Emma.
-我们俩应该谁去呢  -瑞秋
- Which one of us should go to dinner? - Rachel!
事实上  我想或许我们两个都可以去
Actually,I was thinking maybe both of us could go.
哦  真好
Oh, yeah
谢谢  我会多用点心准备你的礼物
Thanks. I'll put a lot of extra thought into your gift.
好了  太棒了  我们全部都可以去
All right,so great,we can all go now.
真棒  你们知道吗
That is fun! Hey! You know what?
我们六个人已经很久没有这样在一起了
We all haven't been together,the six of us,in such a long time.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我们现在就在一起啊
We're together now.
莫妮  钱德勒并不在这里
Mon? Chandler's not here.
噢  老天
Oh,dear God.
大家好  很高兴第一次我们全员到齐
Hello. It's nice to see our team together for the first time.
现在  在我们开始之前
Now,before we get started,
有什么问题要问吗
are there any questions?
-很好  肯  对吧  -没错
- Yes. Ken,is it? - That's right.
有传闻说你之所以会来塔尔萨
Is it true the reason you're in Tulsa is,
是因为你在开会的时候睡着
you fell asleep in a meeting..
然后随口接下此份工作
and took the job
其实你根本搞不清是来干什么的  对吧
without realizing what you were saying yes to?
别道听途说  肯
Well,don't believe everything you hear,Ken.
但是没错  那是真的
But yeah,that's true.
好了  我们先开始
All right,let's get started
看一下上一季的数字
by taking a look at last quarter's figures.
克劳蒂亚  你该先
Claudia,aren't you supposed
问一下老板可不可以抽烟吧
to blow smoke up the boss's ass?
我很抱歉  你介意我抽烟吗
I'm sorry. Does the smoke bother you?
不  我抽了好多年  然后戒了
No. I smoked for years. Then I quit.
现在也忘了为什么要戒
Right now,I can't remember why.
在办公室不准抽烟的  不是吗
You're not allowed to smoke in this office,right?
可以的  在奥克拉荷马
Yes,in Oklahoma
在15人以下的办公室抽烟是合法的
it's legal to smoke in offices with 15 people or less.
你要来一根吗
Would you like one?
好了  听着  我戒烟了
All right,look. I don't smoke anymore.
如果你们其他人也想抽
But if the rest of you want to light up,
请便  没关系的
go ahead,it's fine.
原来你们全部都抽烟
So,you all smoke,then?
其实  我不抽烟反而看起来很没礼貌
You know,it's almost rude that I'm not smoking.
没那回事  如果你不想
That's not true. If you don't want..
肯  拜托
Ken,please!
不  不行  我不能抽烟
No,I can't. I can't smoke.
如果我抽烟  我老婆会杀了我
If I smoke,my wife would kill me.
不好意思  但你老婆不是在纽约吗
I'm sorry,but isn't your wife back in New York?
我一直都很喜欢你  肯
I've always liked you,Ken.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
-嘿  -真是大饱眼福呀
- Hey. - And "treat" it is.
哇  幸好我有换衣服
Wow. So glad I changed.
我差一点就穿上那件
I almost wore my threadbare robe
连胸部都遮不住的破睡袍
that can't contain my breasts.
我不是要穿这件出门  我正在排卵
This is not what I'm wearing. I'm ovulating..
而钱德勒很快就回来了
and Chandler's gonna be home.
所以我觉得可以在晚餐前尝试受孕
So,I thought we would try before dinner.
等一下  这表示你们会迟到吗
Wait,does this mean you'll be late?
相信我  钱德勒和我
Believe me, Chandler and I
已经超过一个星期没有见面了
haven't seen each other in over a week.
我们可能会是第一个到的
We'll probably be the first ones there.
好了  待会见  祝你们搞的愉快
Okay. See you there. Happy humping.
哇  有人在这里抽烟吗
Wow,somebody smoked out here?
天啊  难道他们不知道
My God,don't people know
在公共场所是不可以抽烟的吗
you're not allowed to smoke in public spaces?
事实上  在奥克拉荷马
Actually,in Oklahoma
在少于15人的办公室抽烟是合法的
smoking's legal in offices with fewer than 15 people.
噢  你抽烟了
Oh,you smoked.
不是  我只是刚好知道
No. I just happen to know
不同州的抽烟规定
a lot of trivia about smoking in different states.
例如  在夏威夷
For example,in Hawaii,
香烟叫做雷拉纳路卡斯
cigarettes are called lei-lana-lukus.
钱德勒  你身上都是臭烟味
Oh,Chandler,you stink of cigarettes!
你觉得莫妮卡会闻得到吗
Do you think Monica will smell it?
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
那女人的鼻子像猎犬一样灵
That woman has the nose of a bloodhound.
胸部像希腊女神一样美
And the breasts of a Greek goddess.
菲比
Phoebe?
我要走了
I'm gonna go.
好了  有什么可以掩盖味道
Okay. Something to cover the smell.
炉灶清洁剂
Oven cleaner.
无添加香味
Unscented.
欢迎回来
Welcome home.
我好想你
I've missed you.
想要跟我进房间吗
You want to join me in the bedroom?
不  谢了  不用
No,thanks,I'm good.
好吧  你想玩欲擒故纵  是吗
Okay. So you want to play it that way,do you?
你知道吗  事实上  我才刚下飞机
Well,you know what,actually,I just got off a plane..
觉得有点脏  我应该先洗个澡
so I'm feeling gross. I should take a shower.
过来  你不需要洗澡
Come here,you don't need a shower.
好吧  事实上是
All right,the truth is..
在遇到空中乱流时  我拉屎进裤子了
I soiled myself during some turbulence.
什么味道  我闻到烟味
What do I smell? I smell smoke.
你有抽烟吗
Did you smoke?
有  但是只抽了一根
Yes. But I just had one.
两根
Two.
两小根  好吧  五根
Two tiny cigarettes. Okay,five.
一包  两包  一条
A pack. Two pack.. A carton.
两天抽三大条香烟
Three big fat cartons in two days!
但是都结束了
But it's over.
我已经决定  再也不抽烟了
I've made a decision,I'm not gonna smoke anymore.
那是要送给你的
Well,those are for you.
好的  嗯  到时候见  拜
All right. Well,we'll just see you when you get here. Bye.
噢  是我妈  她遇到大塞车
Oh,that was my mom. She's stuck in terrible traffic.
好吧  这是第三个征兆
Ok, that is now the third sign
告诉我不该离开艾玛
that I should not leave Emma.
另外两个征兆是什么呢
What are the other two?
嗯  第一个是  我不想要
Well,the first one is,I don't want to.
第二个是  我不要去
And second one,I'm not going.
我知道这是我们第一次离开宝宝
I know this is the first time we're leaving the baby.
我知道这对你很困难  但是
I know how hard it is for you. But..
但是一切都会很好的
But everything's gonna be fine.
我是说  我妈会在这里照顾她
I mean,my mom is gonna be with her.
-她很会照顾小孩的 -真的吗
- She's great with kids. - She is?
真的
Yeah.
那莫妮卡是什么情况
What about Monica?
你只听到莫妮卡的片面之词
You only hear Monica's side of that, okay?
那肥妹是个恐怖份子
that little fatso was a terror!
我觉得我办不到
I just don't think I can do it.
瑞秋  你可以的  你也必须那样做
Rach, you know what? You can and you should.
真的  这对你是有好处的
Really,it will be good for you.
事实上  你知道吗
In fact,you know what?
你先去餐厅  我留下来等我妈
Go ahead to the restaurant,and I will wait for my mom..
然后我再过去找你们
and then I'll meet you there.
不  真的  你应该过去  出去
No,no,really,you should go. Go out.
真的  世界都是你的
Really,the world is your oyster.
甩开高跟鞋  挥洒出自己的颜色
Kick up your heels. Paint the town red!
你该学些新的广告词
You need to learn some new slang.
我是说真的  走吧  你该走了
I'm serious. Come on,you should go.
来  去吧
Here. No,just go.
-那 -不  不你知道吗
- Well.. - No,no! You know what?
你别想要进去
You're not getting back in there!
宝宝没事的  现在快走吧
The baby's fine. Now,scram!
跟着你的感觉向前冲
Tell your story walking!
我只是要说  我忘记带钥匙了
I was just going to say that I left my keys.
老天啊  这下我们惨了
Holy moley,are we in a pickle now!
他们人呢  已经迟到四十分钟了
Where is everyone? They're 40 minutes late.
-我知道  -我饿死了
- I know. - I'm starving.
我知道我们今晚要来这里
I knew we were coming here tonight.
所以我整天都没有吃东西
I ate nothing all day.
那我呢  我今天才吃一顿午餐而已
What about me? I only had one lunch today.
那么  其他的贵宾很快就会到吗
So,are we expecting the rest of our party shortly?
是的  我们衷心期盼他们的即将到临
Yes,they are expected presently.
他们  他们即将现身了
Their--their arrival is in the offing.
好的  我们也有两人座的位置
Right. We have a table for two available.
-或许你们  -不用  他们就要来了
- Perhaps you'd.. - No,they're coming.
我们就在这里等
We're waiting right here.
乔瑟夫
Joseph!
您无需担心  他们应该不会太久
One needn't worry. They shan't be long.
我们有一些人在等着要用餐
It's just that we do have some large parties waiting.
您真的有必要这样烦人吗
Oh,one really does have a stick up one's ass,doesn't one?
什么年纪了  竟然还抽烟
How can you smoke in this day and age?
你没有看过反烟广告吗
Have you not seen that ad?
那个小孩穿过他爷爷那个广告
Where the little kid walks through Grandpa?
真是吓死人了
It's chilling!
我搞砸了
I messed up.
当时正开会  每个人都在抽烟
It was a meeting. Everybody was smoking.
那又如何  你难道没有任何意志力吗
So what? Don't you have any willpower?
意志力
Willpower?
我看过你吃巧克力的家庭录影带
I've watched home movies of you eating Ding Dongs..
连包装纸都来不及打开
without taking the tinfoil off!
你说那看起来很性感
You said that was sexy!
好了  好了  可不可以算了
Okay,look,can we just drop this?
我不会再抽烟了
I'm not gonna smoke again.
没错  因为我禁止你抽烟
That's right,because I forbid you to smoke again.
你禁止我
You forbid me?
我大老远飞回来见我可爱的老婆
You know, I've flown a long way to see my loving wife.
对了  她在吗
Is she here,by the way?
钱德勒  别开玩笑  好吗
Chandler,don't joke with me. Okay?
我现在非常非常地不高兴
I'm very,very upset right now.
现在是你最不高兴的时候吗
Is this the most upset you could be?
我想应该是的
I think so.
那  我何不就
Well,then I might as well..
这样做
do this.
不确定接下来要干什么
Not really sure what to do now.
我告诉你我们接下来要做什么
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
我们已经迟了
We're already late
赶不上菲比的生日晚餐了
for Phoebe's birthday dinner.
所以你要把香烟熄掉
So you're going to put out that cigarette..
我们先暂停吵架  先上床再说
we're gonna put this fight on hold,and go have sex.
好  什么
Fine. What?
上床  今天是我排卵的最后一天
Sex! This is the last day I'm ovulating.
如果我们现在不做
If we don't do it now..
我们就要等到下个月了
we're gonna have to wait until next month!
你是认真的吗
You're serious?
噢  是的
Oh,yeah!
随便  做就做  但我不跟你说话
All right,fine,I'll do it,but no talking!
-而且没有抱抱  -而且不亲吻你脖子
- And no cuddling. - And no kissing your neck.
噢  很好  反正我也很讨厌你那样做
Oh,good! I hate it when you do that!
那我要使劲儿亲你的脖子
And lots of kissing your neck!
管理员不在家
Okay,well,the super's not home.
但是我妈很快就到了
But my mother's gonna be here in any minute,
她有钥匙
and she has the key.
我等不了那么久
I can't wait that long.
你得想想办法  把门撞倒吧
You have to do something. Knock that door down!
我也想  但是我就跟桃子一样容易撞伤
I would,but I bruise like a peach.
而且  你知道  一切都会没事的
Besides,you know,everything's gonna be fine.
宝宝在睡觉
The baby's sleeping.
万一她跳出摇篮呢
What if she jumps out of the bassinet?
根本连头都抬不起来  还想跳
Can't hold her head up,but jumped.
噢  天啊  我水龙头还开着
Oh,my God! I left the water running!
瑞秋  你没有让水龙头开着
Rach, you did not leave the water running.
拜托  冷静一点  好吗
Please,pull yourself together,okay?
那  我有把炉子开着吗
Well,did I leave the stove on?
1996年之后你就没有煮过饭了
You haven't cooked since 1996.
窗户有开着吗  如果开着
Is the window open? If the window's open
鸟可能会飞进来然后
a bird could fly in and..
天啊  你知道吗  我想你说对了
My God,you know what? I think you're right.
我觉得  其实  听  听
I think, you know what, listen, listen
是鸽子  不  等等  不
A pigeon. No. No,wait,no.
是老鹰飞进去了
An eagle flew in!
飞到炉子上然后着火了
Landed on the stove and caught fire!
宝宝看到这一切
The baby,seeing this,
从公寓这边跳过去帮助老鹰
jumps across the apartment to the mighty bird's aid.
而老鹰却误认为那是个攻击的行动
The eagle,however,misconstrues this as an act of aggression..
用爪子捉住婴儿
and grabs the baby in its talon.
就在这时候  水龙头的水
Meanwhile,the faucet
充满了整间公寓
fills the apartment with water.
宝宝跟老鹰正熊熊燃烧
Baby and bird,still ablaze,
双方被死亡的陷阱困住
are locked in a death grip..
在公寓内的漩涡里旋转着
swirling around the whirlpool that fills the apartment!
天  如果这一切是真的你就死定了
Boy,are you gonna be sorry if that's true.
-你们好 -嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
已经一个小时了
It's been an hour.
领班要我问你们
The maitre d' asked
是否要考虑换到小桌子
if you'd reconsider switching to a smaller table.
或许我们应该先用餐
Maybe we should just eat now.
在人还没有到齐之前你们不能点餐
You can't order until the entire party's arrived.
餐厅规定
Restaurant policy.
好  那如果说另一桌离开了
Well,how about this? Another table leaves,right..
但是他们的餐盘里还有食物
but there's still some food left on their plates.
那么  餐厅有规定
Okay,what's the restaurant's policy
不能吃那些食物吗
about people eating that?
-那很恶心  -但还是会发生啊
- It's frowned upon. - But it happens.
好了  我要去厕所
All right,I got to go to the bathroom.
不  你不能去
No, you can't go.
不  不  不
No,no,no.
我一个人没办法保住这张桌子
I can't hold this table on my own.
如果他们要我换位子  我会屈服的
If they ask me to move,I'll cave.
如果你要我留下来  我会尿裤子的
Well,if you ask me to stay,I'll pee.
晚上好  小姐
Good evening,miss.
小姐
Miss?
小姐  小姐
Miss? Miss?
好了  算了  我换位子
Okay,fine,I'll move.
好了 你不需要动手动脚的
All right. You don't have to manhandle me.
-哪里  -好的
- Where? - Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
终于  你们到了
Finally. You guys made it.
菲比  这些人是谁
Phoebe,who the hell..?
多花点时间在领带上
Spend more time with the tie!
那样可以生出小孩来
That will make a baby.
听着  我做不到
Look,I can't do this.
我现在没办法跟你做爱
I can't make love to you
我们正吵架呢
while we're fighting this way.
噢  是啊  现在你可真敏感
Oh,sure. Now you're Mr. Sensitivity.
那当初你想在我叔叔丧礼之后做爱时
But when you wanted to have sex after my uncle's funeral..
那是庆祝生命
That was a celebration of life!
好了  我不想这样做  听到了吗
All right,I'm not gonna do this. all right?
你真希望我们的孩子在这种情况下受孕吗
Is this the way you want our baby to be conceived?
不  你是对的
No,you're right.
我们不应该在这种情况下做
We shouldn't do it like this.
反正  我很抱歉
For what it's worth,I'm sorry.
我不应该对你抽烟这件事如此刁难
I shouldn't have come down on you so hard about the smoking.
你是抽了几根烟
So you had a few cigarettes.
又不代表世界末日
It's not the end of the world.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
你真不可思议
You are incredible.
听着  我不会再抽烟了
And listen,I'm not gonna smoke again.
如果我抽  我保证也会
And if I do,I promise I will
隐藏到让你看不出来
hide it so much better from you.
-想吗  -我们来庆祝生命
- Want to? - Let's celebrate life!
好的
Okay!
噢  天啊
Oh,God.
噢  感谢上帝你没事
Oh,thank God you're okay.
我很抱歉我们抛下你
I'm sorry we left.
妈咪再也不会离开你了
Mommy will never leave you again.
再也  再也不会
Never,ever,ever again.
太棒了  我们走吧
Great. So let's get going.
不  我是说真的
No. I mean it.
在经历过刚刚的事之后
After what just happened,
我再也不会离开她了
I'm never leaving her again.
我了解  分离是很煎熬的
I understand. Separation is hard.
有一次我要离开罗斯去美容院
One time I was about to leave Ross to go to the beauty parlor.
他就变得很不开心  他把衣服脱光
And he got so upset he took off all his clothes..
把小鸡鸡夹在双腿间
tucked his willy between his legs..
然后哭喊
and cried out,
"妈咪  我是女生 带我跟你去"
"Mommy,I'm a girl. Take me with you."
然而  时光飞逝
Somehow,over time,
现在跟你分开已经变得容易很多了
it got easier to be apart from you.
不客气
You are welcome.
老实说  我们还是不要说话
You know what? Let's not talk.
什么
What?
我对你抽烟的事还是很生气
I am still so mad at you for smoking!
但你说你已经原谅我了
But you said you forgave me.
只不过是几根烟  没什么大不了的
It was just a couple of cigarettes,no big deal.
我那样说是因为我正在排卵
I just said that because I was ovulating
而你却说
and you said
如果我们在吵架  你是不会跟我做爱的
you wouldn't have sex if we were fighting.
你骗我跟你上床
You tricked me to get me into bed?
没错  我得到我想要的了
That's right. I got mine.
我觉得被利用了
I feel so used.
我想他们不会来了
Well,I guess they're not coming.
你想点餐了吗
You want to just order?
谢谢
Thank you.
服务生
Waiter?
听好了  我会说很快  所以记好
All right,this is gonna go fast,so try to keep up.
意大利扁面配松露切片 以及肋眼牛排
Risotto with shaved truffles and the rib steak..
加上酥炸鸡油菇和波尔多红酒酱
with the golden chanterelles and the Bordelaise sauce..
希望我以上说的不包括"蜗牛"
unless any of that stuff I just said means "snails."
是没有
It does not.
蕃茄馅饼  你建议哪种面呢
Tomato tart,and which of the pastas would you recommend?
两种都很美味
Oh,well they're both exquisite..
两种都要  谢谢
Both it is. Thank you.
我可以有个特殊要求吗
Oh,can I make a special request?
可以什么菜先好了就先端上来吗
Can you bring everything as it's ready?
-前菜  前餐  我们不介意  -嘿
- Appetizers,entrees,we don't care. - Hey!
我可以等你们继续点
I'll wait to put your order in.
你们迟到一个多小时了
You guys are over an hour late.
-发生了什么事  -很抱歉
- What happened to you two? - So sorry.
我们被锁在公寓外面
We got locked out of the apartment.
真是好借口  可以给我吃吗
That's a great story. Can I eat it?
然后瑞秋在犹豫是不是可以丢下宝宝
And then Rachel wasn't sure she could leave the baby.
不是很容易  但今天是你生日
It wasn't easy,but it's your birthday
我做了我必须要做的事
and I did what I had to do.
吧台那边是朱迪跟艾玛吗
And that's Judy over there at the bar with Emma?
那是最好的解决方式
This is for the best.
这样我才不会分心  担心艾玛
I'm not distracted,worrying about Emma..
在家有没有事
how she's doing at home,
我得一心一意跟你们待在这里
and I'm gonna be completely here with you.
噢  她吐了
Oh,she spit up.
-什么  -她吐了
- What?  - She spit up.
朱迪  她吐 朱迪  醒醒  朱迪
Judy? She spit.. Judy,look alive,Judy!
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
每道菜看起来都很美味
Oh,everything looks delicious.
我应该点什么呢  我该点什么呢
What should I have? What should I have?
不能打女人  不能打女人
Never hit a woman. Never hit a woman.
我懂你的意思  菜单实在太棒了
I know what you mean,this menu's incredible.
罗斯像桃子一样容易受伤
Ross bruises like a peach.
他像桃子一样容易受伤
He bruises like a peach.
好了  我要点无花果沙拉 还有鸭肉
Okay,I'll have the fig salad and the duck.
我要点汤跟鲑鱼
I'll have the soup and the salmon.
记住  先做好的就先出  好吗
Remember,whatever comes up first,okay?
-快点  -生日快乐
- Hurry.. - Happy birthday!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
-你们去哪了  -我们刚刚在吵架
- Where have you been? - Well,we had a little fight.
我怎样都不会骗人上床
I would never lie to get someone into bed.
你曾经骗过女生你是肯尼迪家族的人
You used to tell girls you were a Kennedy.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢  哇
Thanks. Wow.
有点挤  不是吗
A little tight,isn't it?
你为什么不订大一点的桌子呢
Why didn't you get a bigger table?
你有订  但他们要你换桌
You had a big table but they made you move.
闭嘴  莫妮卡
Shut up,Monica.
我觉得钱德勒应该想点"烟"熏鸭肉
Oh,well,I suppose that Chandler will have the smoked duck.
而我想莫妮卡应该想点酥"诈"鼠肉
And I suppose that Monica will have the manipulative shrew.
我再让你们考虑一下
I'll give you another minute.
什么  你要去哪
What,where you going?
他说她想要鼠肉的
He said she wanted the shrew!
瑞秋  别这样  艾玛没事的
Rach,come on,Emma's fine.
你已经变成过份关心的母亲了
You're turning into an obsessive mother,okay?
你要停止这样
You need to stop.
你们有听过罗斯他妈
You ever hear the story about when Ross' mom
去美容院的故事吗
went to the beauty salon?
你是说小鸡鸡的事吗
You mean the willy story?
他们早就知道了
They already know it.
我们等你们好久了
You guys, we've been waiting for you for a long time.
-你们应该点餐了 -不  没关系
- Maybe you should order. - No, that's okay.
我已经告诉服务生他们要点什么了
I already told the waiter what they want.
你为什么那样做呢
Why would you do that?
钱德勒  控制一下你的女人
Chandler,control your woman.
好了  既然大家都已经点餐了
Okay,well.. Everybody has ordered.
我想开始今晚的庆祝活动
I would like to start the celebration
先敬菲比一杯
and make a toast to Phoebe.
-她袜子掉了  -什么
- She dropped her sock. - What?
不  不  艾玛的袜子掉了
No. No,Emma dropped her sock.
我今天想约她一起共用午餐的
I wanted to have lunch with her today.
她告诉我她出城了
She told me she was out of town.
她还是没有注意到
She still has not noticed that
婴儿的袜子已经在地上了
the baby's sock is on the ground.
真是敬的好
It's a good toast.
听着  你可不可以提醒一下她呢
Look,will you please get her attention?
妈咪
Mommy?
天啊  朱迪  把袜子捡起来
Oh,for God's sake,Judy,pick up the sock!
捡起袜子  捡起袜子
Pick up the sock! Pick up the sock!
我很抱歉  刚刚很没礼貌吗
I'm sorry,was that rude?
我小小的吼叫
Did my little outburst..
使今晚的难堪更甚一步吗
blunt the hideousness that is this evening?
听着  我知道你们都有自己的事
Look,I know you have a lot going on..
但我想要的只不过是跟我的朋友
but all I wanted to do was have dinner
一起吃晚餐  庆祝我的生日
with my friends on my birthday.
你们全部都迟到
And you are all so late,
而且都不知道礼貌性地打电话通知一下
and you didn't even have the courtesy to call.
现在已经太晚了
Well,it's too late now.
菲比  我想那应该不是我们
Phoebe,I don't think that's us.
噢  这个还没完  你好
Oh,well,this is.. This is not over! Hello?
你们是怎么回事呢
What is going on with you two?
噢  是这样的  我正在排卵
Well,you see,I'm ovulating.
噢  是啊  她自己那样说罢了
Oh,yeah,that's what she says.
或许你根本没有在排卵
Maybe you're not ovulating at all.
或许那只是要拐我上床的借口
Maybe it's a clever ruse to get me into bed.
是啊  烟虫  就是那样没错
Yeah,Smokey,that's what it was.
我就是欲求不满
I just can't get enough.
你们不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this.
她撒谎  她竟然骗我跟她上床
She lied, she ttricked me into having sex with her.
所以呢  你要做爱的  不是吗
So? You got to have sex,right?
我是怎么了  像个女生一样
What's the matter with me? Why am I such a girl?
好了  刚刚是麦克
Okay. That was Mike.
菲比  亲爱的  我们很抱歉
Oh,Phoebe,honey,we are so sorry.
你说的对极了
You are totally right.
我们全心全意在这里
We are here 100 percent..
而且我们爱你
and we love you,
我们已经准备好开始庆祝你的生日了
and we are ready to start your birthday celebration.
你们  这对我实在太意义重大了
You guys,that means the world to me.
好了  我要走了
Okay,I'm gonna take off.
什么
What?
我也爱你们  但是麦克提早下班了
I love you guys too,but,Mike got off work early.
等等
Wait.
我不是那种
I'm not the..
我不是那种会抛下朋友
I'm not the kind of girl that just ditches her friends..
见色忘友的人
to be with her boyfriend.
事实上  我就是
You know what? I am.
再见  大家  朱迪  再见
Bye,guys. Judy! Bye.
如果菲比走了
If Phoebe's gone,
我们可以带艾玛回家吗
can we take Emma home?
我觉得那是个好主意
I think that's a good idea.
我们的保姆刚刚又点了一杯白酒
Our babysitter just pounded another chardonnay.
-再见  -再见
- Bye,you guys. - Bye.
再见
See you.
我想就只剩下我们了
Well,I guess it's just us.
我或许还在排卵
So,I'm probably still ovulating.
你还想再试试看吗
Do you want to give it another try?
你从没有跟肯尼迪家的人上过床吗
So,you've never had sex with a Kennedy,have you?
你们不会就这样跑去做了吧
You're gonna go do it?
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
一旦卵子落到输卵管
Once the egg descends into the fallopian tube..
噢  等等 滚吧
Oh,wait,oh,get out of here!
我诚挚地希望你的朋友会回来
I sincerely hope the rest of your party is returning.
不  只剩下我一个人
No,just me. All alone.
六人份晚餐全给我一个人
Dinner for six for one.
很好  你们将会目睹到
Well,you boys are about to see
一个非常特别的表演
something really special.
-一切都还好吗  -棒极了
- How was everything? - Excellent.
特别是鼠肉  真是美味
The shrew,in particular,was exquisite.
我希望你还有胃口
I hope you've got some room left.
祝你生日快乐  祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
祝你生日快乐  亲爱的
Happy birthday dear...
乔伊  乔伊
Joey. Joey.
乔伊  祝你生日快乐
Joey, Happy birthday to you
这是最棒的生日了
This is the best birthday ever!